toronto-lime.com 2011-11-25

# Toronto-Lime.com

Your privacy is important to us. TORONTO-LIME.com Inc., is committed to maintaining the privacy, security and accuracy of the personal information collected in accordance with applicable legislation. This privacy policy is a statement of principles and guidelines concerning the protection of personal information of the website's users. 

This site contains links to third party websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Our content partner sites may have privacy policies independent of TORONTO-LIME.com. This Privacy Policy extends only to data collected on pages hosted on TORONTO-LIME.com servers. 

Information Collected via User Input:  
Personal information collected by TORONTO-LIME.com is information about an identifiable individual that may include such information as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, birth date and any recorded complaints. Online surveys and contests on our site may ask visitors for contact information and demographic information. We may use contact data from our surveys or contests to send information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners, sponsors or advertisers. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary. Only TORONTO-LIME.com has access to your personal information. Users may opt-out of receiving e-mail communications at any time. 

Information Automatically Collected:  
TORONTO-LIME.com uses your IP address is also used to gather broad, aggregated demographic information. This website uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for the other purposes set out below:

  * We use cookies to remind us who you are and to find your account information in our database when you access a service so you do not need to log in at every visit. This helps us to provide you with service tailored to your specific needs and interests. A cookie is created when you register for a service.

  * We use cookies to estimate our audience size. Your browser is given a unique cookie that helps us determine whether yours is a repeat visit or a first visit.

  * We use cookies to determine the browser the visitor uses so the site can be designed to work properly with the most common versions of different browsers.

  * Our site's registration forms require users to give us a unique username and password. To post a message in www.toronto-lime.com using a form, an email address is also required.

Sharing of Information:  
TORONTO-LIME.com does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. TORONTO-LIME.com retains personal information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 

TORONTO-LIME.com may only share aggregate information with trading partners, and advertisers. However, this aggregated information does not contain personally identifiable information. 

Security:  
TORONTO-LIME.com has reasonable security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and interception by third parties. TORONTO-LIME.com assumes no liability for interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet. 

Contact Us / Email Inquiries:  
No information sent to TORONTO-LIME.com via email or the website forms are used for any other reason than to respond to and maintain a record of the inquiry. This information is not sent to third parties for mailing list purposes.  
For any further inquiries regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact [admin@toronto-lime.com](mailto:admin@toronto-lime.com)
